[
  {
    "question": "食べる",
    "answer": "먹다",
    "hiragana": "たべる",
    "choices": [
      "먹다",
      "읽다",
      "달리다",
      "말하다"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "水",
    "answer": "물",
    "hiragana": "みず",
    "choices": [
      "불",
      "바람",
      "물",
      "흙"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "先生",
    "answer": "선생님",
    "hiragana": "せんせい",
    "choices": [
      "학생",
      "친구",
      "선생님",
      "직원"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "車",
    "answer": "자동차",
    "hiragana": "くるま",
    "choices": [
      "자전거",
      "기차",
      "자동차",
      "버스"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "学校",
    "answer": "학교",
    "hiragana": "がっこう",
    "choices": [
      "병원",
      "학교",
      "도서관",
      "가게"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "犬",
    "answer": "개",
    "hiragana": "いぬ",
    "choices": [
      "고양이",
      "사람",
      "개",
      "토끼"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "猫",
    "answer": "고양이",
    "hiragana": "ねこ",
    "choices": [
      "개",
      "사자",
      "고양이",
      "여우"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "行く",
    "answer": "가다",
    "hiragana": "いく",
    "choices": [
      "오다",
      "가다",
      "걷다",
      "달리다"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "見る",
    "answer": "보다",
    "hiragana": "みる",
    "choices": [
      "듣다",
      "보다",
      "말하다",
      "앉다"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "小さい",
    "answer": "작다",
    "hiragana": "ちいさい",
    "choices": [
      "크다",
      "작다",
      "빠르다",
      "느리다"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "大きい",
    "answer": "크다",
    "hiragana": "おおきい",
    "choices": [
      "작다",
      "예쁘다",
      "크다",
      "빠르다"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "新しい",
    "answer": "새롭다",
    "hiragana": "あたらしい",
    "choices": [
      "낡다",
      "새롭다",
      "좋다",
      "싫다"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "古い",
    "answer": "낡다",
    "hiragana": "ふるい",
    "choices": [
      "낡다",
      "새롭다",
      "빠르다",
      "느리다"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "青",
    "answer": "파랑",
    "hiragana": "あお",
    "choices": [
      "빨강",
      "노랑",
      "파랑",
      "초록"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "赤",
    "answer": "빨강",
    "hiragana": "あか",
    "choices": [
      "빨강",
      "파랑",
      "노랑",
      "검정"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "黄色",
    "answer": "노랑",
    "hiragana": "きいろ",
    "choices": [
      "초록",
      "노랑",
      "하양",
      "보라"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "黒",
    "answer": "검정",
    "hiragana": "くろ",
    "choices": [
      "하양",
      "검정",
      "회색",
      "파랑"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "白",
    "answer": "하양",
    "hiragana": "しろ",
    "choices": [
      "검정",
      "하양",
      "노랑",
      "빨강"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "本",
    "answer": "책",
    "hiragana": "ほん",
    "choices": [
      "펜",
      "책",
      "종이",
      "노트"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "食べ物",
    "answer": "음식",
    "hiragana": "たべもの",
    "choices": [
      "음식",
      "물건",
      "장난감",
      "옷"
    ],
    "level": "N5"
  },
  {
    "question": "便利",
    "answer": "편리하다",
    "hiragana": "べんり",
    "choices": [
      "편리하다",
      "불편하다",
      "위험하다",
      "편안하다"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "地下鉄",
    "answer": "지하철",
    "hiragana": "ちかてつ",
    "choices": [
      "기차",
      "버스",
      "지하철",
      "택시"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "準備",
    "answer": "준비",
    "hiragana": "じゅんび",
    "choices": [
      "준비",
      "복습",
      "예습",
      "복구"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "経験",
    "answer": "경험",
    "hiragana": "けいけん",
    "choices": [
      "경험",
      "감각",
      "지식",
      "기억"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "説明",
    "answer": "설명",
    "hiragana": "せつめい",
    "choices": [
      "질문",
      "설명",
      "요약",
      "응답"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "安全",
    "answer": "안전",
    "hiragana": "あんぜん",
    "choices": [
      "위험",
      "걱정",
      "불안",
      "안전"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "必要",
    "answer": "필요",
    "hiragana": "ひつよう",
    "choices": [
      "불필요",
      "필요",
      "무의미",
      "단순"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "大切",
    "answer": "소중하다",
    "hiragana": "たいせつ",
    "choices": [
      "소중하다",
      "귀찮다",
      "가볍다",
      "작다"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "連絡",
    "answer": "연락",
    "hiragana": "れんらく",
    "choices": [
      "연락",
      "방문",
      "소식",
      "상담"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "時間",
    "answer": "시간",
    "hiragana": "じかん",
    "choices": [
      "장소",
      "기회",
      "시간",
      "목표"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "質問",
    "answer": "질문",
    "hiragana": "しつもん",
    "choices": [
      "답변",
      "질문",
      "요약",
      "감상"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "趣味",
    "answer": "취미",
    "hiragana": "しゅみ",
    "choices": [
      "직업",
      "습관",
      "취미",
      "기술"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "練習",
    "answer": "연습",
    "hiragana": "れんしゅう",
    "choices": [
      "복습",
      "연습",
      "독서",
      "공부"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "友達",
    "answer": "친구",
    "hiragana": "ともだち",
    "choices": [
      "친구",
      "가족",
      "연인",
      "동료"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "運動",
    "answer": "운동",
    "hiragana": "うんどう",
    "choices": [
      "공부",
      "운동",
      "취미",
      "여행"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "掃除",
    "answer": "청소",
    "hiragana": "そうじ",
    "choices": [
      "요리",
      "청소",
      "수리",
      "설계"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "旅行",
    "answer": "여행",
    "hiragana": "りょこう",
    "choices": [
      "공부",
      "운동",
      "여행",
      "독서"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "買い物",
    "answer": "쇼핑",
    "hiragana": "かいもの",
    "choices": [
      "청소",
      "공부",
      "요리",
      "쇼핑"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "食事",
    "answer": "식사",
    "hiragana": "しょくじ",
    "choices": [
      "간식",
      "식사",
      "요리",
      "음료"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "会話",
    "answer": "대화",
    "hiragana": "かいわ",
    "choices": [
      "대화",
      "논쟁",
      "고백",
      "발표"
    ],
    "level": "N4"
  },
  {
    "question": "判断",
    "answer": "판단",
    "hiragana": "はんだん",
    "choices": [
      "판단",
      "결정",
      "감정",
      "이해"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "記録",
    "answer": "기록",
    "hiragana": "きろく",
    "choices": [
      "저장",
      "기억",
      "기록",
      "분석"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "失敗",
    "answer": "실패",
    "hiragana": "しっぱい",
    "choices": [
      "성공",
      "실패",
      "도전",
      "기회"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "発表",
    "answer": "발표",
    "hiragana": "はっぴょう",
    "choices": [
      "발표",
      "대화",
      "회의",
      "토론"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "関係",
    "answer": "관계",
    "hiragana": "かんけい",
    "choices": [
      "관계",
      "원인",
      "상황",
      "조건"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "予定",
    "answer": "예정",
    "hiragana": "よてい",
    "choices": [
      "계획",
      "예정",
      "확정",
      "진행"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "理由",
    "answer": "이유",
    "hiragana": "りゆう",
    "choices": [
      "이유",
      "목적",
      "수단",
      "결과"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "方法",
    "answer": "방법",
    "hiragana": "ほうほう",
    "choices": [
      "도구",
      "방법",
      "결과",
      "과정"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "感情",
    "answer": "감정",
    "hiragana": "かんじょう",
    "choices": [
      "기억",
      "감정",
      "상상",
      "판단"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "希望",
    "answer": "희망",
    "hiragana": "きぼう",
    "choices": [
      "희망",
      "절망",
      "기대",
      "흥미"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "現実",
    "answer": "현실",
    "hiragana": "げんじつ",
    "choices": [
      "상상",
      "현실",
      "소문",
      "환상"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "機会",
    "answer": "기회",
    "hiragana": "きかい",
    "choices": [
      "기회",
      "계획",
      "대안",
      "미래"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "途中",
    "answer": "도중",
    "hiragana": "とちゅう",
    "choices": [
      "시작",
      "도중",
      "완료",
      "중단"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "内容",
    "answer": "내용",
    "hiragana": "ないよう",
    "choices": [
      "형식",
      "내용",
      "표지",
      "정리"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "感動",
    "answer": "감동",
    "hiragana": "かんどう",
    "choices": [
      "감동",
      "기억",
      "이해",
      "지식"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "利用",
    "answer": "이용",
    "hiragana": "りよう",
    "choices": [
      "사용",
      "이용",
      "이해",
      "연결"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "緊張",
    "answer": "긴장",
    "hiragana": "きんちょう",
    "choices": [
      "안정",
      "흥분",
      "긴장",
      "평화"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "責任",
    "answer": "책임",
    "hiragana": "せきにん",
    "choices": [
      "성공",
      "책임",
      "자유",
      "규칙"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "結果",
    "answer": "결과",
    "hiragana": "けっか",
    "choices": [
      "원인",
      "이유",
      "결과",
      "조건"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "誤解",
    "answer": "오해",
    "hiragana": "ごかい",
    "choices": [
      "이해",
      "해석",
      "오해",
      "의심"
    ],
    "level": "N3"
  },
  {
    "question": "条件",
    "answer": "조건",
    "hiragana": "じょうけん",
    "choices": [
      "조건",
      "환경",
      "결정",
      "목표"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "解決",
    "answer": "해결",
    "hiragana": "かいけつ",
    "choices": [
      "문제",
      "해결",
      "진행",
      "설명"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "証明",
    "answer": "증명",
    "hiragana": "しょうめい",
    "choices": [
      "설명",
      "이해",
      "증명",
      "추측"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "適用",
    "answer": "적용",
    "hiragana": "てきよう",
    "choices": [
      "적용",
      "준비",
      "변경",
      "선택"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "調査",
    "answer": "조사",
    "hiragana": "ちょうさ",
    "choices": [
      "검토",
      "조사",
      "판단",
      "결론"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "報告",
    "answer": "보고",
    "hiragana": "ほうこく",
    "choices": [
      "보고",
      "추측",
      "주장",
      "인식"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "手続き",
    "answer": "절차",
    "hiragana": "てつづき",
    "choices": [
      "계획",
      "절차",
      "방식",
      "기획"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "環境",
    "answer": "환경",
    "hiragana": "かんきょう",
    "choices": [
      "상황",
      "환경",
      "조건",
      "배경"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "整理",
    "answer": "정리",
    "hiragana": "せいり",
    "choices": [
      "정리",
      "분리",
      "보관",
      "설정"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "意識",
    "answer": "의식",
    "hiragana": "いしき",
    "choices": [
      "감각",
      "지각",
      "의식",
      "경험"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "対策",
    "answer": "대책",
    "hiragana": "たいさく",
    "choices": [
      "대책",
      "방지",
      "정책",
      "조치"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "管理",
    "answer": "관리",
    "hiragana": "かんり",
    "choices": [
      "경영",
      "감독",
      "관리",
      "통제"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "需要",
    "answer": "수요",
    "hiragana": "じゅよう",
    "choices": [
      "수요",
      "공급",
      "비용",
      "이윤"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "契約",
    "answer": "계약",
    "hiragana": "けいやく",
    "choices": [
      "계약",
      "합의",
      "약속",
      "보증"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "確認",
    "answer": "확인",
    "hiragana": "かくにん",
    "choices": [
      "인정",
      "확인",
      "검사",
      "결정"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "保存",
    "answer": "보존",
    "hiragana": "ほぞん",
    "choices": [
      "보존",
      "보관",
      "저장",
      "보호"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "制限",
    "answer": "제한",
    "hiragana": "せいげん",
    "choices": [
      "한계",
      "제한",
      "경계",
      "범위"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "証言",
    "answer": "증언",
    "hiragana": "しょうげん",
    "choices": [
      "증언",
      "확인",
      "기록",
      "증거"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "尊重",
    "answer": "존중",
    "hiragana": "そんちょう",
    "choices": [
      "존중",
      "관심",
      "협조",
      "복종"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "維持",
    "answer": "유지",
    "hiragana": "いじ",
    "choices": [
      "유지",
      "보존",
      "보관",
      "관리"
    ],
    "level": "N2"
  },
  {
    "question": "抽象",
    "answer": "추상",
    "hiragana": "ちゅうしょう",
    "choices": [
      "구체",
      "일반",
      "추상",
      "단순"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "認識",
    "answer": "인식",
    "hiragana": "にんしき",
    "choices": [
      "감정",
      "지각",
      "인식",
      "기억"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "主観",
    "answer": "주관",
    "hiragana": "しゅかん",
    "choices": [
      "객관",
      "주관",
      "결론",
      "정의"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "証拠",
    "answer": "증거",
    "hiragana": "しょうこ",
    "choices": [
      "증거",
      "가설",
      "주장",
      "의심"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "概念",
    "answer": "개념",
    "hiragana": "がいねん",
    "choices": [
      "개념",
      "정의",
      "분석",
      "설명"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "前提",
    "answer": "전제",
    "hiragana": "ぜんてい",
    "choices": [
      "조건",
      "전제",
      "해결",
      "계획"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "理論",
    "answer": "이론",
    "hiragana": "りろん",
    "choices": [
      "사실",
      "이론",
      "예상",
      "추측"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "仮説",
    "answer": "가설",
    "hiragana": "かせつ",
    "choices": [
      "검증",
      "가설",
      "사례",
      "실험"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "検証",
    "answer": "검증",
    "hiragana": "けんしょう",
    "choices": [
      "확인",
      "실험",
      "검증",
      "관찰"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "構造",
    "answer": "구조",
    "hiragana": "こうぞう",
    "choices": [
      "조직",
      "내용",
      "구조",
      "형식"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "確率",
    "answer": "확률",
    "hiragana": "かくりつ",
    "choices": [
      "기회",
      "가능성",
      "확률",
      "현상"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "概略",
    "answer": "개요",
    "hiragana": "がいりゃく",
    "choices": [
      "개요",
      "예시",
      "해석",
      "요점"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "構成",
    "answer": "구성",
    "hiragana": "こうせい",
    "choices": [
      "구성",
      "요소",
      "통합",
      "집합"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "展開",
    "answer": "전개",
    "hiragana": "てんかい",
    "choices": [
      "정리",
      "진행",
      "전개",
      "설명"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "比較",
    "answer": "비교",
    "hiragana": "ひかく",
    "choices": [
      "차이",
      "대비",
      "비교",
      "대조"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "補足",
    "answer": "보충",
    "hiragana": "ほそく",
    "choices": [
      "요약",
      "해석",
      "보충",
      "정리"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "検討",
    "answer": "검토",
    "hiragana": "けんとう",
    "choices": [
      "검토",
      "반영",
      "조사",
      "연구"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "適応",
    "answer": "적응",
    "hiragana": "てきおう",
    "choices": [
      "적용",
      "적응",
      "반영",
      "반복"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "解釈",
    "answer": "해석",
    "hiragana": "かいしゃく",
    "choices": [
      "요약",
      "설명",
      "해석",
      "비교"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  },
  {
    "question": "前後",
    "answer": "전후",
    "hiragana": "ぜんご",
    "choices": [
      "이전",
      "전후",
      "시점",
      "순서"
    ],
    "level": "N1"
  }
]